{
  "type": "writing",
  "language_code": "zh-CN",
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "Quánshēn",
      "answer": "全身"
    },
    {
      "question": "Shūfú",
      "answer": "舒服"
    },
    {
      "question": "Měi",
      "answer": "每"
    },
    {
      "question": "Duànliàn",
      "answer": "锻炼"
    },
    {
      "question": "Tóu",
      "answer": "头"
    },
    {
      "question": "Téng",
      "answer": "疼"
    },
    {
      "question": "Sǎngzi",
      "answer": "嗓子"
    },
    {
      "question": "Xiǎng",
      "answer": "想"
    },
    {
      "question": "Yīyuàn",
      "answer": "医院"
    },
    {
      "question": "Kànbìng",
      "answer": "看病"
    },
    {
      "question": "Shēntǐ",
      "answer": "身体"
    },
    {
      "question": "Yào",
      "answer": "要"
    },
    {
      "question": "Ba",
      "answer": "吧"
    },
    {
      "question": "Háishì",
      "answer": "还是"
    },
    {
      "question": "Yīqǐ",
      "answer": "一起"
    },
    {
      "question": "Lěng",
      "answer": "冷"
    },
    {
      "question": "Chuān",
      "answer": "穿"
    },
    {
      "question": "Yīfú",
      "answer": "衣服"
    }
  ]
}
